<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parenting on wdputro notes</title>
    <link>https://wdputro.github.io/tags/parenting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parenting on wdputro notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 08:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wdputro.github.io/tags/parenting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summing 3 Years of Fatherhood</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2016-07-09-summing-3-years-of-fatherhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2016-07-09-summing-3-years-of-fatherhood/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Time flies quickly and now he’s turning 3. Since I don’t want to miss memories during this period, allow me to sum these three years in some emotional stages and the circumstances at the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirror, the Forgotten Parenting Buddy</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2016-05-28-mirror-the-forgotten-parenting-buddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 13:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2016-05-28-mirror-the-forgotten-parenting-buddy/</guid>
      <description>Dad :  &amp;ldquo;Son, can you look who&amp;rsquo;s that?&amp;rdquo;   Son :  &amp;hellip;still cryng after his tantrum, he looked at the mirror. &amp;ldquo;He looks&amp;hellip; bad&amp;rdquo;   Dad :  &amp;ldquo;Well boy, that one there is angry!&amp;rdquo;    Knowing yourself is hard. Heck, it’s even harder for children. And as a parent, it is such a constant struggle. I hate myself when yelling to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generation &#39;Y&#39; Legacy: a Parent&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2015-06-12-generation-y-legacy-a-parents-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2015-06-12-generation-y-legacy-a-parents-perspective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a blog post about &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;the ‘unhappy’ Generation Y&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; that being viral in my Facebook timeline. Being part of that generation, I’d say it is relevant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not surprising though that the author brings issue of parenting early in the articles. And the analysis is quite legit. Some might even think simply to blame the parents. After all, it was their fault right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bull.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a Fatherhood lesson from Public Playground</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2015-05-21-a-fatherhood-lesson-from-public-playground/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2015-05-21-a-fatherhood-lesson-from-public-playground/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned the hard way of being a Dad, not in a street fight, but in a Playground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Education Route is best for our Child?</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2015-05-16-which-education-route-is-best-for-our-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2015-05-16-which-education-route-is-best-for-our-child/</guid>
      <description>Which is best for our child, Academic path? Design/Art path? or Both of them?
I would argue, none of them.
Based on my experience who graduated from an engineering degree, then worked as a strategic management staff and afterward founded a business in Packaging Design. I know that most of the problem happens in the workplace is about communication, not hard-skills.
If you put a designer, an engineer and a sales in a closed room with a coffee machine, most of the problem with disappear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anak, Diorama Ayah Bunda</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2014-08-05-anak-diorama-ayah-bunda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2014-08-05-anak-diorama-ayah-bunda/</guid>
      <description>Cempedak diluar pagar, tarik galah tolong jolokkan. Saya budak baru belajar, kalau salah tolong tunjukkan.
 Satu hal yang membuat saya takjub, sekaligus khawatir, adalah betapa anak begitu fasih memproyeksikan karakter dan tingkah laku orang tuanya. Ibarat Diorama, miniatur yang menggambarkan keadaan sesungguhnya dari sebuah landskap, anakmu adalah dirimu… Dan jika kita tidak hati-hati, alih-alih menjadi versi terbaikmu, dia akan menjadi sebaliknya.
Terlihat jelas Alta mewarisi sifat pembelajar dan berkemauan keras dari bundanya, belum mau berhenti sebelum bisa; bahkan marah kalau dilarang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nina Bobo</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2013-07-05-dear-nina-bobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 19:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2013-07-05-dear-nina-bobo/</guid>
      <description>Dear Nina Bobo,
Tidak terasa sudah 1 bulan 7 hari ya? Rasanya baru kemarin kamu menghiasi malamku menemani si kecil. Ya, si kecil Alta buah hatiku.
Aku tahu, terkadang kamu cemburu karena Alta lebih sering mendengar lantunanAl-Qur’an dibanding dirimu, tapi ketika tiba saatnya ia tidur — oh dirimu begitu mengagumkan.
Aku terus mengagumi perkembangan dan kesetiaanmu, bahkan ketika lagumu serta merta kami ubah. Apa daya sahabatku, lirikmu penuh dengan ancaman. Coba dengarkan…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>