<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Urban on wdputro notes</title>
    <link>https://wdputro.github.io/tags/urban/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Urban on wdputro notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 14:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wdputro.github.io/tags/urban/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ambil bayam dari muka bumi, jadilah Salad!</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2012-02-24-ambil-bayam-dari-muka-bumi-jadilah-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 14:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2012-02-24-ambil-bayam-dari-muka-bumi-jadilah-salad/</guid>
      <description>“You are what you eat”
 Demam barang impor..
Begitu bangga dengan merek luar negeri. Membeli demi sekedar gengsi. Sayangnya, tidak berbeda dalam hal makanan.
Pernah memiliki teman yang tidak bisa tidak memamerkan makanan asing yang dibelikan orang tuanya saat sekolah dulu? Padahal cuma pasta.
Pernah memiliki teman yang senang sekali mengunyah selada dengan mayonaise? Padahal cuma salad.
Sejarah makanan tersebut di Indonesia sama dengan kata salad di KBBI: tidak ada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter Jam</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2011-04-22-easter-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2011-04-22-easter-jam/</guid>
      <description>Jakarta April 21, 2011; 09.58 p.m
Hi there, tomorrow is Easter Day and although I’m not celebrating it, I can feel the cheerful atmosphere here at Jakarta. My friends dress fabulous to go to church. Everyone smiles.
Trust me; with maximum level of innocence face, I have to say that this night should be a happy ending.
It turns out to be wrong!
Simple, add three straight holidays at the weekend with the secret recipe: hundreds, probably thousands, of impatience motor and car drivers trying to rush every time the policeman look at the other side of the street; and what do you get?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
