<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Professional on wdputro notes</title>
    <link>https://wdputro.github.io/categories/professional/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Professional on wdputro notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wdputro.github.io/categories/professional/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Portfolios</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/portfolios/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 22:05:28 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/portfolios/</guid>
      <description>These are some personal projects and research publications I have been working on.&#xA;Projects Stage controller GUI Dashboard to connect and control multiple linear stages. Possible to add additional hardware such as oscilloscope and signal generator.&#xA;I built it to create a GUI template for working with multiple hardwares in a measurement.&#xA;Tools used:&#xA;MATLAB GUIDE MATLAB Instrument Control Toolbox Github&#xD;Publications Cherkashin, Maxim, Carsten Brenner, Widodo D. Putro, Benjamin Döpke, Nils C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Widodo Dwi Putro I&amp;rsquo;m working as a Machine Programmer, especially for Laser Machinery&amp;ndash;writing production-ready code using either C#, Python or GoLang. Outside of work, you can find me playing with my sons, training Capoeira or blogging here.&#xA;More info about me? You can connect with me via LinkedIn or GitHub profiles.&#xA;Copyright The articles written in this blog are licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salah Kerja bukanlah Jawaban</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2013-10-28-salah-kerja-bukanlah-jawaban/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 19:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2013-10-28-salah-kerja-bukanlah-jawaban/</guid>
      <description>“Wid, aku merasa tidak nyaman dengan pekerjaanku saat ini. Apa lebih baik aku mengundurkan diri saja ya?”&#xA;Pertanyaan itu diajukan seorang kawan; dan seorang lagi, dan lagi. Izinkan saya berargumen, jangan mengambil keputusan berdasarkan pada emosi. Lagi pula, jarang sekali serta-merta resign begitu saja merupakan solusi terbaik.&#xA;Ada 4 (empat) tips yang bisa kita pakai untuk menghadapi keadaan seperti ini.&#xA;Terima Keadaan&#xA;Hal pertama yang harus dilakukan adalah tarik napas dalam dan bawa diri kita menuju ke keadaan saat ini.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Letter Grup Bakrie</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2012-06-27-ceo-letter-grup-bakrie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 05:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2012-06-27-ceo-letter-grup-bakrie/</guid>
      <description>Assalamu’alaikum wr. wb.&#xA;Salam sejahtera untuk kita semua&#xD;Kepada rekan-rekan karyawan Grup Bakrie,&#xA;Saya tidak sabar untuk segera melaksanakan amanah menakjubkan menjabat sebagai CEO sebuah perusahaan terpandang anak negeri Indonesia, Grup Bakrie. Menjadi bagiannya adalah sebuah kehormatan dan kini saya ingin berbagi optimisme kepada anda akan masa depan gemilang Perusahaan ini.&#xD;Grup Bakrie adalah potret sebuah korporasi yang berakar kokoh mulia. Prinsip ketegasan akan praktek bisnis etis terus dilakoni dan berharmoni dengan nilai sosial yang luas bermuara.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter Jam</title>
      <link>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2011-04-22-easter-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wdputro.github.io/blog/2011-04-22-easter-jam/</guid>
      <description>Jakarta April 21, 2011; 09.58 p.m&#xA;Hi there, tomorrow is Easter Day and although I’m not celebrating it, I can feel the cheerful atmosphere here at Jakarta. My friends dress fabulous to go to church. Everyone smiles.&#xA;Trust me; with maximum level of innocence face, I have to say that this night should be a happy ending.&#xA;It turns out to be wrong!&#xA;Simple, add three straight holidays at the weekend with the secret recipe: hundreds, probably thousands, of impatience motor and car drivers trying to rush every time the policeman look at the other side of the street; and what do you get?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
